黎巴嫩  碧嘉山谷
-拜托...  -闭嘴
- Please... - Shut up!
你们搞错了
You are making a mistake.
都说了我是记者  你们弄错了
I have told you, I am a journalist. You are making a mistake.
和你一起的那女的  难道也是记者
The woman you were with... a journalist, too?
我不知道你指的是谁
I don't know who you mean.
知道间谍的下场是什么吗
Don't you know what we do with spies?
你们搞错了  我是美联社记者
You are making a mistake. I am Associated Press.
你们可以查我的证件
Check my credentials!
那女的在哪
Where is the woman?
去你妈的
住手
卡马里
Kamali.
朱海瑞不肯...
我无条件支持朱海瑞的决定
这你应该明白
他什么都不会说的
我们没时间跟他啰嗦
你们搞错了  我是记者
You are making a mistake. I am a journalist.
我知道你是谁  巴克斯特中士
I know who you are, Sgt. Baxter.
我什么都知道
I know everything.
美国  加利福尼亚北部
跟你说
You see,
在英国有个玩法叫斯诺克
in Britain, we have a game called Snooker,
和一般玩法差不多  不过...
which is similar in many ways; it just, uh,
对技巧和精准度的要求更高
requires a more skillful and delicate touch.
用的球桌更大  而球洞却小得多
It's also played on a larger table with much smaller pockets,
所以玩你们这个...  简单极了
so this is, um, easy.
你当过兵吗
You served?
没  我是个会计
No, ma'am. I'm an accountant.
你们穿得跟条子似的
You boys wear it like a badge.
我在度假
I'm on holiday.
要去多远的地方
How far are you going?
直到没路可走为止
Until we run out of road.
祝你最终能安下心来
May you find peace at the end of it.
干杯
Cheers to that.
爽
Oh, fuck me.
我爱死美国妞了
I love American girls.
你那兄弟去哪了
Where's that buddy of yours at?
那得问问你那漂亮的服务员
You should probably ask that pretty waitress of yours.
那是我女儿
That's my daughter!
你说  "咱们找点乐子"
"Let's have some fun," You said,
"甩掉过去的一切"  这主意真是棒极了
"Let's get away from it all," You said, yeah. Brilliant.
迈克尔  是你说要兜风的
Michael, you wanted to go for a fuckin' walk.
哥们  圣地亚哥之路的风可兜不得
Mate, the Camino de Santiago's not a walk,
圣地亚哥之路是天主教的三大朝圣之路之一
这是荡涤心灵的朝圣之旅  我早就说了
it's a spiritual pilgrimage. I told you that.
你们俩  知道在加州骑车要带安全帽吧
Hey, you boys, you know that California's a helmet state, right?
不  我们不知道这个规定
No, sir, we weren't aware of that.
-我知道  -真的假的
- I was. - Really?
你们还在从阿拉斯加过来的一路上
And you got traffic violations
违反过其他六个州的交通规定
in 6 other states from here to Alaska.
才六个州?
Only 6?
你们是在逃命还是干嘛
You runnin' from somethin'?
Holiday在美语中特指法定节日  而在英式英语中表示度假
我们只是在过节
Uh, we're just on holiday, sir.
-度假  -没错  度假
- Vacation. - Vacation.
他的意思是度假
He means vacation.
请出示驾照和行驶证
License and registration.
那飞机是你们的吗
Does that belong to you?
那是瑞姆吗
Is that Richmond?
真是瑞姆
Fucking Richmond.
他们一定是来找我们的
They're definitely with us.
走了  哥们
See ya, man.
准备好  中士们  假期结束了
Stand to, Sergeants. Leave is over.
-发生了什么  -你胡扯  我们才来好吗
- What's going on? - What're you talking about? We just got here!
迈克尔  帮我跟她说说
Come on, Michael. Back me up on this.
-我们正要南下呢  计划都订好了  -到此为止了
- Look, we're heading south. We have plans. - Not anymore!
-凭什么  -出什么事了
- Why? - What happened?
巴克斯特死了
Baxter's dead!
-什么  怎么死的  -上飞机
- What? How? - Come on.
简报马上就到
Briefing en route.
等等
Wait!
运输机已在空军29棕榈基地待命
Transport waiting at Twentynine Palms airbase.
我这边有情况
I got a situation here.
黎巴嫩  贝鲁特
妈的
Shit.
出去
全都出去
商羯罗  你这个混蛋  给我站住
Not you, Sankara, you sack of shit!
你敢出卖我
You betrayed me.
没有  我发誓
No! I swear!
他们干掉了我一个手下
They murdered one of my men.
你给我交出卡马里
You give me Kamali,
否则我就告诉真主党你是我的奸细
or Hezbollah finds out that you're working for me.
但我不是
But I'm not--
但愿他们会相信你
You better hope they think so.
哥伦比亚  他们去了哥伦比亚
Colombia! They went to Colombia!
哥伦比亚可大得很呢
Colombia's a big fucking place!
卡马里去见戈麦斯贩毒集团和俄国人了
Kamali's meeting the Gomez Cartel and the Russians!
他们准备开战了
They're about to go to war!
你他妈穿件衣服吧  看着就恶心
Put some fucking clothes on. You're disgusting.
准备就绪   中士
Ready, Sergeant.
你要把什么玩意儿弄进我屁股里
What is that you're gonna put in my ass?
是黄热病  破伤风和伤寒的疫苗
Yellow fever, tetanus, typhoid.
你们要去的可是哥伦比亚丛林啊
You're going into Colombian jungle, Sergeant.
病毒比子弹还厉害
You're gonna be dodging more than bullets.
听你这么一说  那就来吧
Seein' as you asked so nicely, Doc, here you go, man.
准备打了
Here we go.
还不赖嘛
That wasn't gel.
知道厉害了吧
Who's your daddy now?
道尔顿少校  他们已准备好接受简报
Major Dalton, they're ready for the briefing now.
欢迎归队  中士们
Welcome back, Sergeants.
巴克斯特的事  想必你们也听说了
I presume you've heard about Baxter.
是的
Yes, ma'am.
以后有的是时间祭奠他的牺牲  但就目前而言
We will have time to mark his death, but as it stands,
我们抓住凶手的机会转瞬即逝
we only have a small window of time to catch the fuck who did it.
白厅：英国政府
瑞姆  白厅在线上了吗
Richmond...Whitehall online yet?
马上接通
Coming up now, Major.
阁下  他们已准备就绪
They're ready for you, sir.
少校
Major.
先生们
Gentlemen.
-该死  -晚上好  上校
- Shit. - Good evening, Colonel.
-是菲利普·洛克  -你认识他
- That's Philip Locke. - What, you know him?
不  只是听说过
No. I know of him.
-没见过  -只说重点
- Never met. - Headlines only.
就在你俩逍遥自在的时候
While you two were away on your little soiree,
一次在贝鲁特的行动出了大问题
an operation in Beirut went badly wrong.
枪杀巴克斯特中士的凶手是这个家伙
Sgt. Baxter's killer is this man--
李奥·卡马里
Leo Kamali.
英国公民  祖籍黎巴嫩
He's a British national, Lebanese heritage.
他是朱海瑞恐怖组织的投资人
Kamali is the money man of the Al-Zuhari terror network
并在幕后指使了这次行动
and the brains of the operation.
由于卡马里  朱海瑞及其组织
Thanks to Kamali, Al-Zuhari and his organization control
向欧洲走私了大量可卡因和海洛因
the supply of most of the cocaine and heroin going into Europe.
道尔顿和巴克斯特负责跟踪他  可是...
Dalton and Baxter were tracking him, and, uh, well...
少校  你还是自己解释吧
care to embellish, Major?
由于侦查监控与情报收集的极不完善
Low-level surveillance, intelligence-gathering.
我们被人暗中摆了一道
We got made somehow.
能关了吗
Can you turn that off?
我们抓住卡马里就等于抓住了朱海瑞
We get Kamali, we get Al-Zuhari himself.
他是本次行动的终极目标
He's the ultimate target of this mission,
我们以前从来没有接近他的机会
and we've never had a chance to get to him before,
可现在机会来了
until now.
虽然没有情报告知朱海瑞的藏匿地点
We have no current intelligence on Al-Zuhari's whereabouts,
但多亏了道尔顿少校  我们得知卡马里现位于波哥大
but thanks to Major Dalton, we know Kamali's currently in Bogota,
但抓住他的机会有限
but our chance to get him is limited.
哥伦比亚依然贪渎腐败  暴力横行
Colombia is still its usual mess of corruption and violence.
不少官员和警察都被贩毒集团收买
Cartels still have politicians and police
所以任何人都不能相信
on the payroll, so there is no trusting anyone.
除了这个女人
Except this woman.
她是金·马丁内斯  美国缉毒局特工
That's Kim Martinez, a DEA agent
她带领的缉毒分队就在靠近贩毒集团老大
running a small narco unit in the jungle near an area
米格尔·戈麦斯管辖区的丛林里
controlled by cartel boss Miguel Gomez.
他正是要与卡马里碰头的人
He's the man Kamali's gonna meet.
我曾与马丁内斯共事  人挺不错
I've worked with Martinez before. She's good.
她非常出色
She's very good.
她会带你们去找他
She'll take you to him.
瑞姆会在波哥大空军基地设立移动"天帐"
Richmond'll set up the Mobile Crib at Bogota Air Force base.
有问题吗
Questions?
要活捉还是就地枪毙
Yeah. You want him dead or alive?
卡马里要抓活的
We want Kamali alive.
有了他的情报  我们就可以摧毁朱海瑞的整个网络
With his intel, we could cripple Al-Zuhari's entire network.
没错
Agreed.
但如果实在抓不到活的...
But if capture's not an option...
格杀勿论
kill him.
-收到  -是
- Roger that. - Yes, sir.
假期结束  小伙子们
The holiday's over, lads.
祝你们好运
Good luck.
还有  道尔顿少校
Oh, and, Major Dalton,
你知道我一直想找机会
you know I've been looking for an excuse
重战沙场
to get some dust on my boots.
千万别给我机会
Don't give me one.
不会的
No, sir.
如果让洛克插手  事态就严重了
If they're bringing Locke into this, it's serious shit.
是吗  他什么来头
Yeah? What's his story?
菲利普·洛克是特种部队的传奇人物
Philip Locke. He's a Special Forces legend.
我在赫里福德受训的时候  他是我们所有人的偶像
When I trained at Hereford, he was the man we all wanted to be.
过去三十年  每项重大行动都有他参与
He's served in every major theater for the last 3 decades.
有传言称他就是在直布罗陀
Rumor has it he was one of the men who
追踪爱尔兰共和军的那个人
went after the IRA on Gibraltar.
明白
Got it.
你觉得他们能完成任务吗
Do you think they're ready for this?
贩毒集团的人可不是吃软饭的
The cartels don't screw around.
他们状态如何
How are they looking?
比你好点  长官
Better than you, ma'am.
这会儿我们本该在巴哈品龙舌兰酒的
We should be fuckin' slammin' tequilas in Baja right now.
迈克  别扯这些了
Don't tell me that, Michael!
妈的
Shit.
20号分部有需要  我们总要回来帮忙的不是吗
The plan was always to come back to Twenty, right?
迈克
Mike?
地上见
See you on the ground.
回头见
See ya round.
说吧  我知道你不吐不快
Go on. Say something.
总部  这里是B组
Zero, this is Bravo team.
已成功着陆  不容易啊
On the ground... finally.
总部  这里是B组
Zero, this is Bravo team.
收到请回复
Do you read me?
-有回复吗  -没有
- You got anything?  - Nothing.
-贩毒集团一定屏蔽了无线电信号  -没错
- Cartel must be jamming the signal.  - Yeah.
行动
Movin' out.
哥伦比亚  卡克塔
妈的
Fuck me.
-迈克  -什么事
- Mike.  - Yeah?
哥伦比亚  波哥大空军基地
下士
Corporal.
准备好了吗
Are we up yet?
通讯将在20分钟后恢复
Got comms online in 20 minutes.
-什么问题  -信号问题
- What's the problem?  - Signal issues.
-迅速解决  -是  长官
- Get it sorted.  - Yes, ma'am.
我需要确保"天帐"的可用性
I need the Crib operational.
斯科特和斯顿布奇已抵达目标国  需要支援
Scott and Stonebridge are in country and need support.
我需要获悉他们的位置  并取得无线电联络
I want their location and I want radio contact.
竟降落在这个鬼地方
Dropped into some shit hole like this.
鬼知道周围藏着什么病毒
Fuckin' God knows what diseases around.
非要抓这个混蛋家伙
Pick some bad-ass hombre,
抓到了又如何
and for what?
地球少了他照转不误
World's just gonna keep on turnin',
还是会有其他坏家伙接替他的位置
and some asshole's just gonna replace him.
我们这也算扶其他混蛋上位啊  老兄
We're in the bad-ass hombre-making business, buddy.
简直是为其他蠢蠢欲动的人创造机会
Fuckin' job creators.
我们的工作并不是寻因求果
Ours is not to reason why.
或许我们现在应该改变一下
Well, maybe it's time we start.
我已烦透了这项工作
I'm gettin' sick of this shit.
我他妈只是想赢  懂吗
I just want to fuckin' win, you know?
没有所谓的输赢  我们依然...
There's no win. You know that. We still--
那他妈的是什么
What the fuck was that?
-可能是一条寄生鲶  -那是什么鬼东西
- Probably a candiru.  - What the fuck's that?
一种会游进你的鸡巴里吸血的鱼
The little fish that swims up your cock and drinks your blood.
钻进去就弄不出来了  那鱼身上有倒刺
You can't get it out. It's got barbs.
你他妈胡说八道什么东西
You fuckin' kiddin' me?
-我是认真的  老兄  -有疫苗吗
- No, mate. - We get a vaccine for that?
不用担心  老兄
Nothin' to worry about, mate,
你鸡巴这么短  它找不到的
'cause it'll never find your tiny cock.
滚你妈的
Fuck you.
我想出去了
I want to get out now.
B组  这里是总部  无线电检查  完毕
Bravo, this is Zero. Radio check, over.
不行  B组  这里是总部
On it. Bravo, this is Zero.
无线电检查  完毕
Radio check, over.
总部  这里是B组
Zero, this is Bravo Team.
无线电信号不太好  完毕
Difficult radio check, over.
我们能追踪到你们的位置  但通讯可能不太清楚
We can track you, but clear comms are gonna be hard.
与马丁内斯的汇合点位于你们北向两公里的位置
You're two clicks south of the rendezvous with Martinez.
耐力不错
Good bearing.
是谁出卖了我们
Who betrayed us?
起来  你这个混蛋
Get up, you bitch!
名字
A name.
我只需要知道名字
That's all I want from you.
叛徒的名字
A name.
把叛徒的名字告诉我
去你妈的
塞巴斯汀·格瑞
上校  你对"塞巴斯汀·格瑞"这个名字有印象吗
Colonel, what does the name Sebastian Gray mean to you?
格瑞
Gray?
他以前是军情六处的人
Well, he was with MI6.
他八十年代在贝鲁特领事馆工作
He worked out of the Beirut consulate in the eighties,
但后来召他回来的时候  他却消失了
but when they recalled him, he vanished.
直到两年前
Up until two years ago,
他将情报卖给出价最高的买家
he was selling intel to the highest bidder,
后来他惹恼了法国  便转入地下工作
but then went to ground when he pissed off the French.
他们派了一支队伍进行暗杀  我们认为他已经死了
They sent a team in to get him. We thought he was dead.
我有强烈的预感他还活着
Yeah, well, I have a pretty strong feeling he isn't.
必须把他找出来
Need to find him.
我会把所有情报都发给你  但都已经过时了
Well, I'll send you what we can, but it's past its sell-by date.
如果你们发现他的踪迹  一定要避免正面接触
And if you do find him, approach from downwind.
一旦他有所察觉  你是怎么都捉不住他的
He sees you first, you've lost him.
给我订下一班飞贝鲁特的机票
Get me on the next flight to Beirut.
马上就办  长官
Right away, sir.
你好  先生
你好啊
就你一个人吗
Are you alone?
举起手来
Hands up.
-看来你那武器不是用来钓鱼的  -防身用的
- I take it that weapon's not for fishing.  - Protection.
在这一带  你永远摸不透那些愚蠢的鬼佬
Around here, you never know when some dumb gringo
什么时候会从树林里窜出来
will come out of the jungle.
或许我应该向你介绍我的朋友
Perhaps I should introduce my friends, huh?
同志们好
Gentlemen.
你迟到了
You're late.
我认为你们有两个人
I thought there was two of you.
他在这呢
There is.
金·马丁内斯
Kim Martinez.
真人果然更有魅力
Even lovelier in the flesh.
你那些花言巧语还是省省吧
Don't try that charm shit on me.
你伙计会说话吗
This one talk?
如果有话说  我还是会说的
When I have something to say, yeah.
你们是洛克上校队里的  是吧
So you're Colonel Locke's team, huh?
出发前最好让你们熟悉一下情况
Well, we better get you briefed before you go
免得你们栽在这丛林里其他人的手上
stumbling into somebody else in the jungle.
并不是所有人都像我这么热心的
Not everybody's as warm-hearted as me.
我喜欢她
I like her.
我就知道
You would.
听着如果你们想要卡马里
Listen, if you boys want Kamali,
就得从这个人身上下手
you're going to have to take him from this guy--
米格尔·戈麦斯
Miguel Gomez,
前哥伦比亚警长
former Colombian police commander.
他叛变了?
He changed sides?
有钱能使鬼推磨
Money'll do that.
戈麦斯曾是个铁面警察
Now, Gomez was a brutal cop,
但他现在完全成了大反派
but he is in a whole 'nother
搞起了自己的贩毒集团
league now he's running his own cartel.
他称自己为美洲豹
He calls himself "The Jaguar."
这都是他的地盘
All this is his.
有重兵把守
It's heavily guarded and patrolled,
但洛克上校说你俩必须完成任务
but Colonel Locke tells me you guys get the job done,
那就需要深入敌后作战
operating behind the lines.
对  这事非我们莫属
Yep, that's us.
这还分敌前敌后?
There's a line?
卡马里一年只来一两次
Kamali's here only once or twice a year,
而且我们知道
and we know he's key to
他是将集团资金向国外转移的关键人物
moving the cartel's money out of the country.
现下戈麦斯已经召集了
Now Gomez has called together all
集团各部的老大与俄国的武器贩子接头
the cartel bosses to meet with a Russian arms dealer.
我猜  这是卡马里的命令
My guess--it was on Kamali's orders.
戈麦斯家在距这东南向两公里的地方
Gomez's place is two clicks southeast.
找个合适的侦查点  天黑再行动
Find a suitable O.P., wait till dark.
就这么定了
Sounds like a plan.
李奥
Leo.
米格尔  我的朋友
Miguel, my friend.
很高兴见到你  好久没见了
It's good to see you. It's been too long.
你总是无事不登三宝殿
Seems like you only come to see me now when there are problems.
他们都到了吗
Are they all here?
你是最后一个了
You're the last.
我这儿有娱乐活动
I have entertainment.
你没必要带自己的女人来
You didn't need to bring your own puta madre.
她叫赛琳  米格尔
Her name is Celine, Miguel,
她不是为"美洲豹"来的
and she is not for The Jaguar.
-这位是维克多?  -是的  维克多来了
- Viktor? - Yeah, Viktor is here,
阿卡帝没来
not Arkady.
他是个大麻烦
He can make it a problem.
我们这儿有很多不受欢迎的人  李奥
We have a lot of unhappy people here, Leo.
我们需要冲锋陷阵的铁汉子  而不是博人欢心的猴子
We expected the organ grinder, not the monkey.
有时候猴子比较容易控制
Sometimes the monkey is easier to control.
维克多  还记得我的朋友李奥吗
Viktor, you remember my friend Leo.
我记得
I do.
代我向你的父亲问好
Do remember me to your father.
他是个伟大的人
He is a great man.
他没能前来真是遗憾
It's a shame he couldn't be here.
我可以全权代表我的父亲
I speak for my father in all things.
有什么问题吗  大兵
Is there a problem, soldier?
寄生鲶
Candiru.
这些小鱼会游进...
You know, those little fish that swim up--
这里没有
Not here.
这又不是亚马逊
It's the Amazon.
混蛋
Asshole.
我本不该来这儿的
I shouldn't be here.
我本没有来这儿的必要
I shouldn't have to be here,
我很确信的告诉在座的各位
and that I am must surely tell us
有些事出了岔子
that something is not as it should be.
我们的行动
Our activities
受到了前所未有的关注与审查
are under more scrutiny than ever before.
每个部门  每支警力
Every agency, every police force
都在对我们进行强力打击
bring their strength against us,
可我们还是占尽上风
and yet we prevail.
这是怎么做到的?
How?
因为我们团结一致
Because we are united in our efforts.
分裂会毁了我们
Division will destroy us.
缺乏信任也会毁了我们
Lack of trust will destroy us,
而我不会容忍这些情况的发生
and I will not tolerate it.
朱海瑞不会容忍这些情况的发生
Al-Zuhari will not tolerate it.
"善恶有报"这话到底是谁说的
Who says crime doesn't pay, huh?
塔楼上有四个
I got 4 on the towers.
空地上有六个
I got at least 6 on the ground.
关于你答应一周前运抵的那些军火
Am I right in believing that Samuel has paid you
我相信塞缪尔已经把运费付给你了吧
for the arms shipment which you agreed to deliver a week ago?
你很清楚你的那些破船在哪
You know where your fucking ship is
你也知道船不在这的原因
and you know why it's not here.
李奥  你所谓的尊重在哪呢
Leo, you talk about respect?
你害我损失了两名最优秀的部下
Two of my best men killed, huh?!
这是真的吗
Is this true?
塞缪尔说那些俄国佬
Samuel says that the russians
强奸并杀害了他的一名妓女
raped and murdered one of his whores
所以他就把他们全杀了作为惩罚
and he had them killed in return.
-马丁内斯  -什么事
- Martinez. - Hmm?
你想干掉那些守卫  掩护我们撤退吗
Want to take out the guards, cover our exfil?
怎么不让我顺便也把卡马里抓来给你
Why don't I just go in and grab Kamali for you, too?
在我们撤退时分散敌人的注意就行了
A distraction for our exfil will be great.
没问题
You got it.
没问题?
"You got it."
他开口你就"没问题"?
He gets "You got it"?
他很有礼貌
He's polite.
除此之外  他那伦敦腔迷死我了
Besides, that British accent kills me.
有一个办法能让我们重归于好
There is a way for us to make a peace,
但需要以牺牲为代价
but it is through sacrifice that we progress.
当然了  维克多
Of course, Viktor,
那批货你必须送到
you will deliver the shipment.
我保证阿卡帝会耳闻你出色的外交手腕
I'll ensure Arkady will hear of your diplomacy,
他一定会为自己的儿子感到自豪的
and he'll be proud of his son.
塞缪尔
Samuel...
我可不会去做那该死的...
Hey, I'm not going to do a fucking...
你要为你的行为做出检讨
You will make redress for your actions,
而我们都将学会什么叫尊重
and we will all learn a new respect.
把他弄出去
我们进去时动静小点
So let's go in soft, let's grab Kamali,
抓了卡马里就走  尽量别跟他们打起来
and let's leave, try not to start a war here.
明白
Copy that.
停
Stop it!
停  等等
Stop. Hold on.
达米恩
Damien.
瑞贝卡
Rebecca.
你他妈在这干什么
What the fuck are you doing here?
你说我在这儿还能做什么
What do you think I'm doing here?
你说你退出了
You said you were out.
你说过要远离摩萨德  远离杀戮
You said no more Mossad, no more killing!
我因此才放你走的
I gave you that out!
你以为这真如嘴上说的那么容易吗
Did you really believe it was gonna be that easy?
上帝啊
Jesus Christ.
这就是我们的宿命
This is what we do.
你呢
And you?
我是来找李奥·卡马里的
I'm here for Leo Kamali.
呵呵
Ha.
"呵呵"
"Ha."
你呵什么呵
What's that mean?
多谢老兄  多谢
Gracias, brother, gracias.
卡马里是我的
Kamali's mine.
放屁
Bullshit.
你知道我为了接近这人都做了些什么吗
Do you have any idea what I had to do to get close to this guy?
我看得很清楚  瑞贝卡
Yeah, I got a pretty fair idea, Rebecca.
你知道他是什么人吗
Do you even know who he is?
当然知道  他是真主阿拉的银行家
Yeah, of course I do. He's Allah's banker.
那么你以为我在这是为了什么
So why do you think I'm here?
为了帮助摩萨德除掉他吗
What? So Mossad can disappear him?
去你妈的  他杀了我们的人
Fuck that. He killed one of ours.
我必须把他带走
I'm taking him.
达米恩
Damien,
别他妈给我添乱
do not fuck this up.
我差一点就能得到...
I am this close to getting somethi...
-赛琳  -该死
- Celine? - Fuck.
赛琳
Celine?
你把门锁上了?
You locked the door?
我不喜欢这些保镖看我的眼光
I don't like how these bodyguards look at me.
他们让我觉得我只是个下贱的妓女
They make me feel like one of those cheap hookers.
我和你一样  也不喜欢这些人
I don't like these people any more than you.
但这还是必要的
It's necessary.
我会补偿你的
I will make it up to you.
我保证
I promise.
现在不行
以后我们有的是时间
我爱死了你说阿拉伯语的模样
I love it when you speak Arabic.
别
No.
晚上好啊
Buenas noches.
这算什么  家庭聚会吗
What is this, a fuckin' family reunion?
吃醋了
Pretty harsh.
想得美
Not really.
要穿衣服吗
Want to get dressed?
-你犯了一个很大的错误  -让他闭嘴
- You're making a big mistake. - Shut him up.
你这么做很愚蠢
You don't know what you're doing.
不  他只是看起来比较蠢
No, he just makes it look that way.
你听我说  你得...
You have to listen to me. You have--
不需要  谢谢
No, I don't.
你在干什么
妈的
Oh, shit.
站起来
不  不  不
No, no, no, no, no.
别冲动
我是你们的人
你就穿这身衣服?
The fuck you wearing?
你还指望我带军服吗
You think I brought my fatigues?
从这撤退
This the exit.
只等洛克找的小妞办完事
As long as Locke's little buddy's done her job.
D组  我们需要分散敌人注意
Delta, need that distraction.
你们不能带他走  卡马里是我的
You can't do this. Kamali's mine.
除非有一组摩萨德的人
Unless you got a Mossad team out there
伪装成树蛙蹲在这
disguised as tree frogs,
否则他就是我们的人了
he's ours. Oh, yeah.
没错  她们总有点小秘密瞒着你是吧
It's always the little things they don't tell you, huh?
比如她是个以色列特工?
Like she's an Israeli agent?
D组请回复  D组  汇报行动进展
Delta, come in, Delta. Delta, how about that distraction?
D组  收到请回复
Delta, come in. Do you copy?
D组  请回复
Delta, respond.
没有回应
Nothing.
斯科特  转移阵地
Scott, moving.
喂  你给我过来
Oy, come here!
你他妈说什么
What the fuck?!
-过来  -你知道我他妈是谁吗
- Come here. - Do you know who the fuck I am?!
我不在乎  过来伙计
I don't care who you are. Come here, mate.
别
Don't!
走
Moving.
操
Fuck.
跟上  跟上  快
Follow me, follow me! Move!
跟紧了  跟紧了
Just follow me, just follow me!
维克多
Viktor!
Viktor.
看来你还能分清敌我嘛
You remember whose side you're on, huh?
快撤  快
All right, you guys got to start moving! Move!
我们走
Go!
-那人是谁  -说来话长  快撤
- Who the hell is that? - It's a long story. Move!
撤
Moving.
借过  借过
Excuse me. Excuse me.
见鬼
Damn it!
想逃跑没门
The only way you leave here
除非对你的脑袋开一枪
is with a bullet in your head.
快给我跟上
Now fucking move.
跟上
Move!
别开枪
Don't shoot.
他们还没发现我们
They haven't made us yet.
天呐
Oh, God.
快回来
Come here!
马丁内斯
Martinez!
-快  -妈的
-Move! -Fuck!
瑞贝卡  到这来
Rebecca! Down there!
-天呐  -站住
- Oh, God. - Halt!
马丁内斯
Martinez!
回来  回来
Come here! Come here!
快过来
Come here!
跟着我
Follow me!
马丁内斯  快给我回来
Martinez! Get back here!
-来了  -操
- Moving! - Fuck!
阿迈  9点方向
Mikey! 9 o'clock
他妈的  斯科特  来了
Fuck! Scott, moving!
手雷
Grenade!
干的好
Good work.
这里是B1  收到请回复
Bravo One. Do you copy?
This is Brave One. Come in.
总部  我们需要立即撤退
Zero, we need an exfil now.
没有回应
Nothing.
-该死  -我们只能靠自己了
- Fuck. - We're on our own.
别抬头
Stay down.
迈克  山上有增援
Mike! More coming on the ridge!
拖住他们
Catch it!
他妈的  人家说了挡不住那么多嘛
Fuck! Told you I couldn't cover 'em!
隐蔽  隐蔽  趴下
Move! Move! Move! Down!
迈克尔
Oh! Michael!
干嘛
Yeah?
你们海军喜欢游泳对吧
You Navy boys like to swim, right?
没错
Yeah.
想去抢那艘船吗
You want to go get that boat?
行啊  干吧  管他妈的  干嘛不
Yeah, let's do it! What the hell? Why not?
瑞贝卡  你在后面掩护我们
Rebecca! You cover us back there!
他要去干什么
What the hell is he doing?
不成功便成仁
Something brave or something stupid.
现在还说不准
Can't tell yet.
快  撤退
Go! Move!
迈克尔
Michael!
我们来了  我们从侧翼过去
I'm coming to you! We'll go around!
瑞贝卡  往河边走
Rebecca! To the river!
瑞贝卡  去河边
Rebecca! The river!
他妈的
Fuck!
去还是不去
Well, go or don't go!
你自己选
Your choice!
走
Move!
快走
Come on!
Go! Move!
快走  快  迈克
Let's go! Run! Mike!
他妈的  好了  用那个重机枪
Fuck! All right! Get on the 30-cal!
把他拉上船
Help him in!
快点  撤
Come on, go, go!
狗日的去吃屎吧
Fuckin' eat shit!
干得漂亮  潜水侠
Nice work, Aquaman!
赶快开回家去
Now take us home!
他妈的  开什么国际玩笑
Oh, come on! Are you fuckin' kiddin' me?!
该死
Oh, shit!
-马丁内斯  准备好了吗  -没问题
- Ready, Martinez? - You got it.
就是现在
Now! Now!
你他妈快用重机枪啊  斯科特
Fuckin' fire up that 30-cal, Scott!
来了
I'm on it!
都去吃屎吧
Fuckin' piece of shit!
他妈的  重机枪没子弹了
Fuck! 30-cal's out.
-阿迈  -什么
- Mikey! - Yeah?
我用佩枪了  你那边怎样
I'm down to my sidearm. How are you doing?
船没动力了  斯科特  没动力了
Fuck! I'm losing power, Scott! Losing power!
马达被打坏了
The engine's hit!
我们要想其他办法了  伙计
We need a Plan B, mates!
找到了好东西
Fuckin' awesome!
你还有C4炸药吗
You got any C4 left?
-继续再做一个  -好
- Get going on that next one. - OK.
－迈克尔  -干嘛
－ Michael! - Yeah?
到这儿来
Get down here!
马丁内斯  给我一个弹匣
Martinez, throw me another mag!
把好舵
Take the wheel.
没问题
Got it.
好了  我扔你射
All right! I throw, you shoot!
数到一还是数到零
On one or zero?
闭上你的臭嘴  射就是了
Shut the fuck up and shoot it!
该死
Shit!
他妈的  你射偏了
Fuck! You missed!
你这蠢货居然射偏了
I can't believe you fuckin' missed!
你给我扔准了  我就能射中
You fuckin' throw it right, I'll fuckin' hit it!
扔
Go!
-去死吧  -太棒了
- Fuck you! - Fuck, yeah!
干得好  迈克尔
Nice work, Michael.
射得好
Nice shooting. Whoo!
炸弹做得好
Nice bomb-making.
-你还好吗  -没事
- You all right? - Yeah.
总部  这里是B组
Zero, this is Bravo Team.
能听到吗
Do you read me?
B组  这里是总部  听得很清楚  完毕
Bravo, from Zero, good check, over.
报告情况
Sit-rep?
场面有点混乱  不过我们拿到了"包裹"
It's a little hairy. We got the package.
很好  带他回来
Good work. Bring him in.
趴下  趴下
Get down! Get down!
趴下  狗日的
Get down! Shit!
把船开出这里
Get us out of here!
妈的  又来了
Oh, shit! Incoming!
趴下
Down!
B组  收到请回复
Bravo, come in.
Bravo Team, respond.